vipoutlet.com 2019-05-29

# VIPOUTLET.com Privacy Policy - VIP Outlet

VIPOUTLET.com is operated by Direct Liquidation LLP (“we,” “us,” “VIPOUTLET” or “VIPOUTLET.com”). All necessary precautions are taken to ensure the privacy of our visitors/customers. Listed below is an outline of the data collected and its use as defined in VIPOUTLET’s Terms of Service (<https://www.vipoutlet.com/terms-conditions)>.

By visiting VIPOUTLET.com, you acknowledge and agree to the procedures detailed herein. Please direct all questions regarding this policy and/or terms to support@vipoutlet.com.

## Collected information by VIPOUTLET.com

Two (2) types of data are collected from every visitor to VIPOUTLET.com: (i) information supplied by the visitor (including information offered when creating an account with us, such as name and contact details), and (ii) data collected by VIPOUTLET.com as you access the website.

The data collected by VIPOUTLET.com as you access the website relates to identifying your browser type and Internet Protocol (IP) address, as well as certain data from your browser cookies (information regarding your browsing session recorded by your browser on your local machine).

It is necessary to access Session ID cookies in order to determine an account holder is logged into the website; cookies are removed once the browser has been closed.

An optional (though enabled by default) ‘persistent’ cookie is used to record your login username (not your password); thereby, allowing quicker login. This convenience feature can be disabled via your browser settings at any time.

Additional information may be collected such as: pages viewed, resources accessed, general traffic data, location data and other communication data to improve the performance features of the VIPOUTLET.com.

It is a violation of VIPOUTLET.com’s Terms of Service to misuse any information provided or collected from VIPOUTLET.com. Violations must be reported to [support@vipoutlet.com](mailto:support@vipoutlet.com). Terms of Service can be found at <https://www.vipoutlet.com/terms-conditions>. By using VIPOUTLET.com, you agree the above mentioned information can be collected/transferred/processed within the United States.

## Children Under Age 18

VIPOUTLET.com does not knowingly collect or ask for any personal information from persons under eighteen (18) years of age, nor are they knowingly allowed to become registered users on the site. Please do not attempt to create an account or send any information (such as your name, address, telephone number and email address) to VIPOUTLET.com you are under eighteen (18) years old.

If VIPOUTLET.com becomes aware of any information held is of a person under eighteen (18) years of age, it will be immediately deleted. Please contact us at [support@vipoutlet.com](mailto:support@vipoutlet.com) if you believe VIPOUTLET.com may hold any information of a person under eighteen (18) years of age.

## Use of Information

Information collected is used to provide services in the following ways:

  1. Your name and email address may be used on occasion to send you information about any new services that you may have interest.
  2. Notifications on the general running of VIPOUTLET.com.
  3. Your information may be shared with qualified third parties for the purpose of: general traffic trends, personalizing advertisements, and for promotions. These relationships offer extended     benefits while protecting privacy.

## Sharing Information with Third Parties

User information, share with qualified third parties without obtaining future user permission, is only shared when:

  * When reasonably necessary provide services via VIPOUTLET.com (such as is stated in the Privacy Policy).
  * When legally required or to prevent illegal activity.
  * To protect VIPOUTLET.com’s name, trademarks, and intersts/property
  * To prevent bodily harm.
  * When users have given specific permission. For example: 
    * Facilities for servers that support VIPOUTLET.com.
    * Information on new/expanded services.
    * Removal of unnecessary information from user lists.
    * Payment processing.
    * Search engine results (including sponsored links).

Personal information may be accessed, for a limited time and use, by qualified third parties in order to provide services and is protected under your user agreement. Qualified third parties are; but not limited to, trade partners, lawyers, agents, or government agencies. If the whole, or a substantial portion of VIPOUTLET.com transfers ownership, collected information will fully transfer to the new owner to ensure service is not interrupted/ VIPOUTLET.com will continue normal operations. If this occurs, all information will remain subject to this Privacy Policy.

## Links

VIPOUTLET.com may include sponsored lines to partner sites. VIPOUTLET.com maintains no control over the privacy practices of these sites. Users are encouraged to read the privacy policies prior to providing information via the linked sites. This Privacy Policy only applies to the information VIPOUTLET.com collects.

## Third-Party Advertising

Advertisements shown on VIPOUTLET.com may be delivered directly by third parties. To enable this, third parties may (i) receive your IP address, (ii) download cookies onto your computer, (iii) use other software in order to measure how effective their advertisements/to personalize advertisements sent. No third party will have access to any of your contact information unless you give your permission.

Our use of cookies is covered under this Privacy Policy; however, the use of cookies or tracking technologies used by advertisers is not covered. We do not have access to; nor control over, data collected by third parties.

## Security

Precautions are taken to protect account information. All account information is located behind a firewall on a secure server. Whenever you enter sensitive information, such as credit card number or your account password, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

Never send private information via email and/or instant messaging services. These, and other forms of social communication, are not recognized as secure forms of communication. If you have any security questions relating to VIPOUTLET.com, please contact us at [support@vipoutlet.com](mailto:support@vipoutlet.com).

## Terms of Service

Any use of VIPOUTLET.com, or disputes arising from its use, are subject to both this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service found at <https://www.vipoutlet.com/terms-conditions>.

## Revisions to this Privacy Policy

VIPOUTLET.com retains the right to alter, modify, and or update this Privacy Policy and its Terms of Service at any time and without prior notice. Immaterial amendments will take effect immediately and material amendments will take effect 30 days after posting on VIPOUTLET.com. If at any time the Privacy Policy is edited, the effected date will be clearly stated at the top of the page.

Users should regularly visit the Privacy Policy to ensure you are aware of and understand the current terms of the Privacy Policy. Unless expressly stated, the Privacy Policy for VIPOUTLET.com applies to all information regarding your account.

## Disclaimers

DIRECT LIQUIDATION LLP, Inc., its directors, employees, content providers, affiliates, and all other representatives will not be held liable for any damages (including lost profits, consequential, or punitive damages) unless specifically stated in this Policy, any other location on VIPOUTLET.com or required by law, for any problems arising from your use, failure to use, or performance of VIPOUTLET.com, or its contents. Any damages related to use of this website are at the expense of the user.

## Contacting Us

Any questions regarding this policy or terms herein should be referred to our privacy staff at [support@vipoutlet.com](mailto:support@vipoutlet.com).
